A Christmas Kiss is a tv movie, romance, family film directed by John Stimpson.
Wendy Walton is the best designer in Boston...
but no one knows it yet.
Hoping to kick-start her career, Wendy has left work with the local theatre to take a job as
an assistant to Priscilla Hall, the most prestigious designer in the city.
Hall works Wendy around the clock, which is how Wendy finds herself trapped in
an elevator late one night with an incredibly handsome stranger.
Wendy and the mystery man share an impulsive, romantic, life changing kiss
before the doors open and Wendy runs out, leaving him behind.
The next day at work, Wendy answers the door to find the
handsome gentleman standing in front of her.
Priscilla Hall, played by Elisabeth Röhm.
Wendy Walton, played by Laura Breckenridge.
Adam Hughes, played by Brendan Fehr.
Tressa, played by Jerrika Hinton.
Caroline, played by Laura Spencer.
Charlie, played by Mark Joy.
A Christmas Kiss is a 2011 American made-for-TV romance film directed by John
Stimpson and starring Elisabeth Röhm, Laura Breckenridge and Brendan Fehr.
Written by Joany Kane, the film is about an aspiring interior designer who has a chance encounter with
a handsome stranger, with whom she shares an impulsive romantic kiss in an elevator.
Later she discovers that he is the wealthy socialite
boyfriend of her callous and dominating employer.
While decorating and preparing his home for an upcoming holiday charity fundraiser, they get to know
each other, and soon he must decide which woman holds the key to his future happiness.
Filmed on location in Richmond, Virginia, A Christmas Kiss first aired
on December 11, 2011 on the Ion Television network.
The tone is emotional.